Finding Aid for Michigan United Conservation Clubs records, 1937-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan United Conservation Clubs records 1937-2004
Michigan United Conservation Clubs.
87139 Bn 2
Federation of state conservation and environmental organizations. Administrative files, including minutes of board of directors and executive committee; press releases and other published materials; files of district organizations and of various organization committees; and photographs.
24 linear feet
2 oversize volumes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records of the Michigan United Conservation Clubs (Donor No. 7413 ) were first donated on January 22, 1987. Periodic additions have been received.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The Michigan United Conservation Clubs (MUCC) was formed November 9, 1937 in Owosso, Michigan. The organization was created to bring together into a federation various clubs in the state that were interested in conservation issues, particularly in regards to conservation legislation. Thirty-six clubs were represented at the first meeting. Harry Gaines of Grand Rapids was elected to serve as the group's first president. Dues were set at fifteen cents per capita on the membership of each member club.
The organization expanded rapidly, growing to 81 clubs during its first year, and to 143 by the beginning of the Second World War. During this period, some of the clubs disbanded as members were called into military service. By 1944 the number of affiliated clubs had leveled off at 128. It was also during this period that the MUCC formed a magazine committee which began publishing Michigan-Out-of-Doors in 1947. Today the MUCC is the largest statewide conservation organization in the nation.
Though conservation of Michigan's natural resources has always been the primary focus of MUCC's work, the organization has also involved itself in issues concerning outdoor recreation. In earlier years the term outdoor recreation referred mainly to activities such as swimming, camping, hiking, fishing, hunting and the like. In the past two decades the proliferation of vehicles such as motorcycles, all-terrain vehicles (ATV's) and snowmobiles has added an entirely new dimension to the meaning of outdoor recreation. MUCC has taken a leading role in advising the state legislature on both of these matters and has striven to keep up with new trends throughout its fifty-year history.
The education committee is one of the most important of MUCC's standing committees, stemming from the organization's belief that ultimately the most effective method to resolve conservation/recreation issues is through education of the public. Teacher education (in cooperation with the Department of Natural Resources), providing speakers to schools and public gatherings, and a one-week camping/conservation program at the MUCC Boy's Camp are some of the ways in which MUCC aims toward greater public understanding of conservation issues.
At MUCC's annual conventions, members gather to discuss amendments to the organization's bylaws, reports of committees (both standing and ad-hoc), and resolutions, which are then brought before the state legislature if adopted at the convention. Indeed, this is the origin of much of the conservation legislation passed by the Michigan legislature.
The records of the Michigan United Conservation Clubs have been divided into the following series: Administration, Committees, Correspondence, District Organizations, Public Relations, Speech File, Topical Files, Publications, Visual Materials, People File, and Scrapbooks.
Subjects:
Conservation of natural resources--Michigan.; Environmental protection--Michigan.; Michigan United Conservation Clubs.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Conservation of natural resources--Michigan.; Michigan United Conservation Clubs.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Motion pictures.; Videodiscs.
- Administration
  The Administration series consists of a copy of the organization's constitution, bylaws, and amendments. There are also board of directors meeting minutes, 1965-2004; executive committee meeting minutes, 1962-2001; annual convention agendas, reports, and meeting minutes, 1937-2001; a handbook for MUCC officers, fund-raisers, etc.
  - Annual reports 1984, 1986-1992, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Annual reports to National Wildlife Federation 1976-1978 (Box 1)
  - Audit Reports 1950/51-1977/78, 1989-1990, 9 folders (Box 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes
    - 1965-1983 (Box 1)
    - 1984-1996 (Box 13)
    - 1997-2004 (Box 14)
  - Conservation Fund-raiser of the Century 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    (Includes Photographs)
  - Constitution; bylaws and amendments 1993, 1997-2000, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Convention
    - Index to Resolutions undated (Box 2)
    - Minutes and Reports
      - 1937-1949, 13 folders (Box 2)
        (lacking 1945)
      - 1950-1954, 8 folders (Box 2)
      - 1955-1962, 9 folders (Box 2)
        (lacking 1958)
      - 1964-1972, 17 folders (Box 3)
      - 1973-1979, 14 folders (Box 4)
      - 1980-1992, 22 folders (Box 11)
      - 1993-2001, 12 folders (Box 12)
  - Convention Award Winners 1951-1981 (Box 12)
  - Corporate and Administrative Policies and Procedures 2000 (Box 12)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes 1962-1973, 7 folders (Box 12)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes 1974-1982, 1985-1989, 1991, 1995-2001, 18 folders (Box 5)
  - Fantasy Raffles undated, 1996-2000 (Box 5)
  - Focus Group 1998 (Box 5)
  - Financial Statement 1987 (Box 5)
  - Fundraising Ideas 1998-2001 (Box 5)
  - Fundraising Targets / Michigan Environmental Organizations 2000 (Box 5)
  - Handbook for MUCC directors, chairmen, and District Field Representatives (Box 5)
  - Investment Policy (Box 5)
  - Leadership Training (Box 5)
  - Legal Department Materials 1994, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Reports 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - License to Solicit and Pledge Forms 2000 (Box 5)
  - Membership Survey 1997 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Banquets and Fund-raisers 1996-2002 (Box 5)
  - Mission Statements / History of MUCC 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - MUCC Handbooks/Reports 1962-1992 (Box 5)
  - Officer and Board Lists 1937/38-1959/60, 1966/67-1969/70, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Public Relations Specialist Job Description July 2000 (Box 5)
  - Resolutions, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Resolutions-Edge 2 (Box 5)
  - Resolution-Bentley Historical Library (Box 5)
  - Report on Financial Statements 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Revenue Analysis of Major Problems 1996-2000 (Box 5)
  - Revenue Enhancement Team Meeting 2000 (Box 5)
  - Staff Organizational Chart undated (Box 5)
  - Strategic Planning, "2000 and Beyond" (Box 5)
  - Strategic Plan Development / Management Team 2001 (Box 5)
  - Time Study November 2000 (Box 5)
- Committees
  Committees consist of an alphabetically arranged listing of MUCC committees spanning the years 1959-2001. The material on these committees, some of them standing and others ad-hoc, consists of meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, and memoranda.
  - Awards 1991-2001 (Box 6)
  - Dues 1989-1999 (Box 6)
  - Education 1977-2001 (Box 6)
  - Energy 1981-2002 (Box 6)
  - Environmental Protection December 1979-September 1983 (Box 6)
  - Equal Access Rights 1989-1999 (Box 6)
  - Finance and Budget 1994-1995, 1999-2000 (Box 6)
  - Fisheries 1979-1997 (Box 6)
  - Fisheries, Salmonid Report 1988 (Box 6)
  - Forestry 1982-2000 (Box 6)
  - Government Reorganization
    - Interim Report of Ad Hoc Committee on Government Reorganization February, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on State Government Reorganization as Related to Environment and Resource Management undated (Box 6)
    - Transfer and Consolidation of Environmental Functions Within the Department of Natural Resources-Executive Order 1973-2 January 11, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Review of Governor Milliken's Executive Order, 1973-2 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence and memoranda February 1971-September 1975 (Box 6)
  - Headquarters Expansion 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Hunter Education 1996-1997, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Hunter Safety March 1980-October 1981 (Box 6)
  - Officer and Board Expense Ad Hoc 1996 (Box 6)
  - Outdoorama 1983-1997 (Box 6)
  - Pittman-Robinson Ad Hoc 2000 (Box 6)
  - Population 1992, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Public Access 1982 (Box 6)
  - Publications, Minutes 1959-1997 (Box 6)
  - Publications, Miscellaneous Paperwork 1961-2002 (Box 6)
  - Rare II 1978 (Box 6)
  - Recreation October 1977-June 1981 (Box 6)
  - Recreational Vehicle October 1971-June 1976 (Box 6)
  - Roadside Beauty and Litter Control November 1961-March 1977 Statewide Cleanup, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Salaries and Benefits 1996, 2000 (Box 15)
  - Selection 1996 (Box 15)
  - Site 1988, 1995, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
  - Special Events 1969-1973, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Sports Show 1991-1997, 2001 (Box 15)
  - Trial Grounds 1981-1996 (Box 15)
  - Various 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Water Rights June 1979-August 1983 (Box 15)
  - Water May-November 1978 (Box 15)
  - Ways and Means 1976, 1984-1996 (Box 15)
  - Wildlife 1977-1996 (Box 15)
  - Women in Outdoors 1995-1997 (Box 15)
  - Youth Activities 1992-2000 (Box 15)
- Correspondence
  The Correspondence series is arranged chronologically and consists primarily of copies of outgoing correspondence with a scattering of incoming communications as well as some administrative memoranda and legal materials.
  - Undated 1935, 1946, 1969-1970, 1977 (Box 15)
  - 1986-1988, 13 folders (Box 15)
  - January-August 1989, 8 folders (Box 7)
  - September 1989-December 1990, 10 folders (Box 7)
  - 1996, 2001 (Box 7)
- District Organizations
  The District Organizations series contains correspondence, meeting minutes, and memoranda from sixteen of the twenty statewide districts that make up the structure of MUCC. These materials span the dates 1970-2000.
  - Affiliation and Disaffiliation Lists 2000 (Box 7)
  - Club Due Increase Memo 2000 (Box 7)
  - Club Events 2000 (Box 7)
  - District 1 February 1970-July 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 2 January 1980-November 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 3 November 1979-November 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 4 May 1973-February 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 5 August 1980-December 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 6 August 1979-December 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 7 March 1980-May 1982 (Box 7)
  - District 9 February 1980-December 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 10 January 1980-November 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 11 January 1980-December 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 14 May 1980-September 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 15 October 1980-November 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 16 April 8, 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 17 May 1980-December 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 19 September 1978-March 1981 (Box 7)
  - District 20 February 1980-December 1981 (Box 7)
  - Region I (Upper Peninsula) Materials 1974-1988 (Box 7)
  - Region IV (East Michigan) 2000 (Box 7)
- Public Relations
  Public Relations, 1968-2001, consists of press releases, 1970-2001, five publications written by MUCC members and published by the organization, four folders of miscellaneous brochures, and a wide variety of materials relating to the publication of the MUCC magazine Michigan Out of Doors. The Bentley Library has on microfilm an almost complete run of this magazine, minus some issues destroyed in an office fire. This microfilm has been cataloged separately.
  - Advertising and Underwriting Sales Agreement Amendment May 23, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Mailing Leads / Marketing April 2000 (Box 7)
  - Media Contact Form 2000 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Out-of Doors Magazine (MOOD) publication files
    - Authorizations 1989-1997 (Box 7)
    - Cartoons (Box 7)
      (Ken Lowe)
    - Circulation Reports 1993-2000 (Box 7)
    - Content and Cost Analysis 2001 (Box 7)
    - Editorial Meetings, undated 1996 (Box 7)
    - Issue Records / Advertising 1999 (Box 7)
    - Press Run System 1993-1997 (Box 7)
    - Press Run System 1998-2000 (Box 7)
    - Publisher (R.R. Donnelley) 1995-2001 (Box 7)
    - Subscription Card Analysis 1993-1998 (Box 7)
    - UPC Codes 1982-1999 (Box 7)
  - MUC Club Quarterly, Summer, Fall 2000 (Box 8)
  - Newsletters 1944, 1955, 1961 (Box 8)
  - Press releases
    - Undated (Box 8)
    - March-August 1970 (Box 8)
    - February-October 1971 (Box 8)
    - January-November 1972 (Box 8)
    - June 1973, 1975-1979 (Box 8)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 8)
  - Brochures, 4 folders (Box 8)
- Speech File
  The Speech File series contains 123 general speeches that are indexed by the list in the "General Speech Index" folder, and other speeches relating to wildlife management, gun control, etc. There is also a small file of correspondence.
  - Correspondence 1977-1993 (Box 8)
  - General Speeches undated, 1973-1992
    - Index to Speeches no. 1-123 undated, 1973-1992 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 1-10 1975-1977 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 11-20 1974-1975 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 21-35 1972-1975 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 36 (various speeches) 1971-1981 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 37-50 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 51-65 1976-1979 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 66-80 1977-1983 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 81-95 1981-1986 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 96-111 1986-1989 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 112 (miscellaneous speeches) 1987-1991 (Box 8)
    - Speeches no. 113-123 1988-1992 (Box 8)
  - Notes and Miscellaneous undated, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Speeches on Conservation undated, 1964-1993, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Speeches on Gun Control and the NRA undated, 1990-1995 (Box 8)
  - Speeches on MUCC undated, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Speeches by Richard Jameson (and résumé) undated, 1991-1998 (Box 9)
  - Speeches by Tom L. Washington undated, 1986-1994, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Speeches on Wildlife Maintenance undated, 1972-1993, 3 folders (Box 9)
    (see also Anti-Hunt files in Topical Files series)
- Topical files
  Some of the subjects documented in the Topical Files include material on the organization's fiftieth and sixtieth anniversaries, history, Kent County Conservation League, and the case of Michigan v. Paul C. Younger 1949 relating to the right of a conservation officer to search a suspect. Two of the strengths of this series are the Anti-Hunting and Indian Fishing Rights.
  - Anti-Hunt File 1971-1995
    - "Animals into Meat: A Report on the Pre-Slaughter Handling of Livestock," March 1971 (Box 9)
    - Anti-Hunting Articles undated 1993, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Anti-Hunting Organizations undated 1975 (Box 9)
    - Anti-Hunting Publications undated 1995, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - The Big Sky, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
    - Cleveland Amory / Fund for Animals 1971-1977 (Box 9)
    - Committee for Humane Legislation-Statement by Bernard Fensterwald April 25, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence undated 1994, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Deer Reports undated 1975 (Box 9)
    - "How do we Achieve and Maintain variety and optimum numbers of Wildlife?" A Symposium at the National Wildlife Federation Annual Meeting March 30, 1974 (Box 9)
    - "Hunting: Sport or Sin?" University of Wisconsin-Stevens Point September 14, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Lorne Greene undated 1975 (Box 9)
    - Mailings and Propaganda undated 1987 (Box 9)
    - [Proposal to Combat Anti-Hunting / Anti-Gun Movement] 1975 (Box 9)
    - Proposals undated 1980 (Box 9)
    - Ranger Rick 1974 (Box 9)
    - Reports and Statistics 1974-1992 (Box 9)
  - Clubs Information (Box 16)
  - Conservation Organization for Youth Outdoor Training and Exploration (COYOTE) 2000-2001 (Box 16)
  - Conservation Reinvestment Act (CARA) 2000 (Box 16)
  - Fiftieth anniversary 1987 (Box 16)
  - Grand River Expedition Certificate 2000 (Box 16)
  - History/historical materials 1937-1987, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - Indian Fishing Rights
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 16)
    - Michigan Out of Doors Articles (Box 16)
  - Kellogg Conservation Club Handbook 1940-1941 (Box 16)
  - Kent County Conservation League 1921-1959 (Box 16)
  - Kuras Properties 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Michalski, Louis 1965-1973 (Box 16)
  - Michigan Natural Resources Magazine 1981, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Michigan v. Paul C. Younger (right of conservation officer to search suspect) 1949 (Box 17)
  - Michigan State University Development Council 1994, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - Michigan United Conservation Clubs' Energy Advocacy Project 1992 (Box 17)
  - MNTRF Grants by County 1978-present 1997 (Box 17)
  - National Shooting Sports Foundation (NSSF) (Box 17)
  - Patches from Various Conservation Leagues and Game Clubs (Box 17)
  - Proposal D and Proposal G 1996
    (protection of scientific wildlife management in Michigan and defeat of animal rights extremism)
    - Campaign Packet (Box 17)
    - Post Election Survey and Statewide Tracking (Box 17)
  - Report on Great Lakes Water Quality 1981 (Box 17)
  - Rouman, James L. 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Sixtieth Anniversary-Information Resource Kit 1997 (Box 17)
  - Trippensee, Reuben Edwin 1983 (Box 17)
  - Washington (Tom)-Biographical and NRA miscellaneous 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Website (Box 17)
  - Wetlands Watch 1998-2000 (Box 17)
- Publications
  The Publications series contains a non-contiguous run of the periodical Michigan Out of Doors.
  - Michigan Out of Doors Magazine 1970-1978 (Box 18)
  - Michigan Out of Doors Magazine 1970-1978 (Box 19)
    (continued)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series contains a variety of photographs depicting various public figures, wildlife, and organizational activities, nine 16 mm films, a videodisc, and a small assortment of slides. The bulk of the photographs are a subseries taken by Richard P. Smith.
  - Illustrations: Laurie O'Keefe 2006 (Box 20)
  - Photographs
    - People
      - Groups, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Single (Box 20)
      - 1972 Convention (Box 20)
    - Buildings (Box 20)
    - Richard P. Smith
      (prominent Michigan photographer and author)
      - Alewife (Box 20)
      - Bear, Black, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Beaver (Box 20)
      - Bobcat (Box 20)
      - Bow Hunting (Box 20)
      - Coyote (Box 20)
      - Crow (Box 20)
      - Deer, White-Tailed, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Dove (Box 20)
      - Duck (Box 20)
      - Eagle (Box 20)
      - Elk (Box 20)
      - Falcon (Box 20)
      - Fish Planting (Box 20)
      - Fisher (Box 20)
      - Fishing
        - Baits (Box 20)
        - Bass (Box 20)
        - Brook Trout (Box 20)
        - Brown Trout (Box 20)
        - Crappie (Box 20)
        - Chinook (Box 20)
        - Coho Salmon (Box 20)
        - Great Lakes (Box 20)
        - Herring (Box 20)
        - Ice (Box 20)
        - General (Box 20)
        - Lake Trout (Box 20)
        - Menominees (Box 20)
        - Muskellunge (Box 20)
        - Perch (Box 20)
        - Northern Pike (Box 20)
        - Panfish (Box 20)
        - Rainbows (Box 21)
        - Salmon (Box 21)
        - Splake (Box 21)
        - Steelhead (Box 21)
        - Sturgeon (Box 21)
        - Sucker (Box 21)
        - Walleye (Box 21)
        - Whitefish (Box 21)
      - Fox, Red (Box 21)
      - Goose, Canada (Box 21)
      - Grouse
        - Ruffled (Box 21)
        - Sharp-tailed (Box 21)
        - Spruce (Box 21)
      - Hare, Snowshoe (Box 21)
      - Heron, Great Blue (Box 21)
      - Hunting
        - General (Box 21)
        - Bear (Box 21)
        - Deer (Box 21)
        - Ducks (Box 21)
        - Rabbits (Box 21)
        - Squirrel (Box 21)
        - Turkey (Box 21)
      - Indian Fishing (Box 21)
      - Jay, Gray (Box 21)
      - Lamprey, Sea (Box 21)
      - Logging (Box 21)
      - Moose (Box 21)
      - Mushrooms (Box 21)
      - Muskrat (Box 21)
      - Muzzleloading (Box 21)
      - Oak Trees (Box 21)
      - Opossum (Box 21)
      - Owls (Box 21)
      - Pheasant (Box 21)
      - Porcupine (Box 21)
      - Porcupine Mountains (Box 21)
      - Quail (Box 21)
      - Rabbit, Cottontail (Box 21)
      - Raccoon (Box 21)
      - Rail, Yellow (Box 21)
      - Robin (Box 21)
      - Salmon (Box 21)
      - Shooting (Box 21)
      - Skunk (Box 21)
      - Squirrels (Box 21)
      - Smelt (Box 21)
      - Smith's Print Files (Box 21)
        (composites of images)
      - Swan (Box 21)
      - Sylvania Tract (Box 21)
      - Tick (Box 21)
      - Trout (Box 21)
      - Woodcock (Box 21)
      - Turkey, Wild (Box 21)
      - Turtles (Box 21)
      - Weasel (Box 21)
      - Whitefish Point (Box 21)
      - Wolf (Box 21)
      - Wolverine (Box 21)
      - Woodchuck (Box 21)
  - Motion Pictures, 16 mm
    - History of MUCC 1960 (Box 10)
    - MUCC Presents Camp Ludington February 29, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Outdoorama at the Armory 1975 (Box 10)
    - MUCC Groundbreaking at 2101 Wood, Dedication, November 1970 (Box 10)
    - Adventure Out of Doors, Jack Van Coevering Producer, Program No. 7, Dude Ranch / Trout Fishing in Glacier Park, 19-2? (Box 10)
    - Mill Lake MUCC Youth Camp 1981, silent, color, run time: 10 minutes (Box 10)
    - MUCC-The Golden Years undated, silent (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled film (Box 10)
    - Wounded Deer, The Detroit News December 20, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Slides
    - 1979 Convention, 2 boxes (Box 10)
    - 1985 Outdoorama, 1 boxes (Box 10)
  - Videodisc (Box 10)
    (marked "For Museum")
- People File
  The People File series contains an alphabetical arrangement of persons affiliated with the MUCC, as well as political figures. The files themselves contain photographs and additional background information sporadically throughout the series. There are two distinct sizes of envelope files (9x6 and 8.5x11) that contain various sizes of photographs.
  - 9x6 Envelopes
    - Ammann, G. A. (Andy) (Box 22)
    - Bobier, Bill (Box 22)
    - Bodem, Beverly A. (Box 22)
    - Bolle, Bob (Box 22)
    - Bonior, David E. (Box 22)
    - Bonno, Lois (Box 22)
    - Bontekoe, Ryan (Box 22)
    - Borkovich, Bruce W. (Box 22)
    - Borkovich, John D. (Box 22)
    - Borkovich, Michael L. (Box 22)
    - Bouchard, Michael (Box 22)
    - Boucher, Cara (Box 22)
    - Bowerman, Bill (Box 22)
    - Boyce, Arlow (Box 22)
    - Brackenridge, Robert L. (Box 22)
    - Bramble, Barbara (Box 22)
    - Brater, Elizabeth (Box 22)
    - Breen, Robert (Box 22)
    - Brett, George (Box 22)
    - Brickley, James H. (Box 22)
    - Briggs, Wendell (Box 22)
    - Brodhead, William H. (Box 22)
    - Brotherton, Wilbur V. (Box 22)
    - Brown, Basil (Box 22)
    - Brown, Dr. Frederick L. (Box 22)
    - Brown, Mary (Box 22)
    - Browne, Bill (Box 22)
    - Bruce, James (Box 22)
    - Bryant, James A. (Box 22)
    - Bryant, William R., Jr. (Box 22)
    - Buchner, George (Box 22)
    - Buck, James (Box 22)
    - Bullard, Perry (Box 22)
    - Bullard, Willis, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Burgoyne, George (Box 22)
    - Burke, Abbie (Box 22)
    - Burke, Robert D. (Box 22)
    - Burkhalter, Larry E. (Box 22)
    - Burns, Gloria M. (Box 22)
    - Burns, Owen C. (Box 22)
    - Bursley, Gilbert (Box 22)
    - Busch, J. Michael (Box 22)
    - Bush, Eric (Box 22)
    - Buth, Martin D. (Box 22)
    - Butterfield, Jack (Box 22)
    - Byker, Gary (Box 22)
    - Byl, William R. (Box 22)
    - Byrum, Dianne (Box 22)
    - Cameron, Bruce (Box 22)
    - Campbell, David L. (Box 22)
    - Campbell, James (Box 22)
    - Campbell, John (Box 22)
    - Carl, Doug (Box 22)
    - Carlson, Elton C. (Box 22)
    - Carlson, G. Hilding (Box 22)
    - Carnaghi, Leonard (Box 22)
    - Carollo, E. R. (Gene) (Box 22)
    - Carr, Bob (Box 22)
    - Carroll, Nancy E. (Box 22)
    - Carter, Harlon B. (Box 22)
    - Case, Frederick W., Jr. (and Roberta) (Box 22)
    - Cawthorne, Dennis (Box 22)
    - Chafee, John (Box 22)
    - Chamberlin, Alice (Box 22)
    - Chapin, Roy D. Jr. (Box 22)
    - Charles, Gordon (Box 22)
    - Charters, Keith (Box 22)
    - Cherry, Deborah L. (Box 22)
    - Cherry, John D., Jr. (Box 22)
    - Churchill, Sally (Box 22)
    - Ciaramitaro, Nick (Box 22)
    - Cihelka, Milos (Box 22)
    - Cisky, Jon (Box 22)
    - Clack, Floyd (Box 22)
    - Clapper, Louis S. (Box 22)
    - Clark, Laura (Box 22)
    - Clark, William P. (Box 22)